upmyrank.com 2018-01-06

# Give Your Alexa Rank A Boost

The purpose of UpMyRank.com is to take advantage of Internet technology to enable businesses to interact with each others websites and in turn increase each members current Alexa rankings. As such, privacy is at the core of UpMyRank.com. 

The statement below outlines our privacy program. It is a work in progress. From time to time, as we expand our services, we will update our privacy policy but the underlying goal of protecting our members' privacy will remain. We also welcome your continuous input into these guidelines. Give us your feedback at [privacy@UpMyRank.com](mailto:privacy@upmyrank.com). 

**About Us**

All information collected as a result of your membership in UpMyRank.com will be controlled by UpMyRank.com, a California corporation. UpMyRank.com may transfer or share your information within the UpMyRank.com group of international subsidiaries ("UpMyRank.com Group") as part of a transfer of your membership agreement. It will only do this to improve the administration of the services. At all times the companies that make up the UpMyRank.com Group ("We") will follow this privacy policy. 

We do not give, sell, rent, share, or trade any identifiable personal information regarding our members to any third party, with the exception of third-party contractors and service providers who work with UpMyRank.com to provide the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program and other services, and who are strictly prohibited from later use of the information that they may have access to. We will disclose personal information to local, state, or federal law enforcement officials when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. 

**Information We Collect**

In our online registration form, we require you to provide us with your full name, email address and a password.  We will process this information to administer your membership, determine your eligibility for certain services such as the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program, provide services to you, and enable you to take advantage of other member benefits. 

While you are using the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program, you will be accessing other members websites. YOU CAN CLOSE THE UpMyRank AutoSurf Program WINDOW AT ANY TIME TO STOP SURFING MEMBER SITES. 

**Cookies**

The process we use to serve member sites and issue credits to the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program involves use of a "cookie." A cookie is a piece of text that can be entered into the memory of your computer. It helps UpMyRank.com and our advertising service track the frequency and placement of site views. Many Internet services deliver cookies to visitors of their Web sites. Cookies store information about your use of their service on your computer where it can only be retrieved by the same service at a later time. Cookies are used by Internet services to make their services much more convenient and personalized. 

Our UpMyRank AutoSurf Program uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same sites repeatedly and to save your username and password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you connect to the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program. 

Most cookies are "session cookies," meaning that they are automatically deleted at the end of a session. You are always free to decline our cookies, if your browser permits, or to ask your browser to indicate when a cookie is being sent. You can also delete cookie files from your computer at your discretion. Note that if you decline our cookies or ask for notification each time a cookie is being sent, your UpMyRank AutoSurf Program may not function properly and we may have difficulty rendering service to you. 

If you would like more information about cookies, you may wish to do a search on Yahoo or visit <http://www.cookiecentral.com/>. 

**Our Use of Your Information**

We use your email address to verify your identity and protect against fraud and to contact you when you are eligible to download upgrades of the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program. In addition, we use it to send you updates about your account, and company updates.  We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. 

**Our Disclosure of Your Information**

UpMyRank.com may share non-personal aggregate, or summary, information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties. Further, we can - and you authorize us to - disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate. 

**Site Viewing Notice**

When visiting other members websites on the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program. These websites may place cookies on your computer. 

**External Links**

The UpMyRank AutoSurf Program™ delivers members Web sites to your computer. UpMyRank.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We use industry standard procedures and processes to safeguard the confidentiality of your identifiable personal information, such as firewalls, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data. Unfortunately, when you submit information about yourself to UpMyRank.com over the Internet the information may travel over many systems that are not under the control of UpMyRank.com. The Internet is not 100% secure and others may intercept the information that you are sending. One easy and important way to protect your personal information is to guard your account password and close your browser and UpMyRank AutoSurf Program windows when you step away from your computer. 

**Consent to Process Your Personal Data**

UpMyRank.com members constantly have the option to enter and exit the UpMyRank.com service at any time and for any length of time. Members who participate in the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program™ Service have the opportunity to opt-in to receive promotional/marketing information via the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program from our partners at any time, simply by opening the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program. By opening the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program, You consent to having the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program record data which will be used by UpMyRank.com in accordance with this policy. To opt-out, You may simply close the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program. Members are always free to close their account by sending an email to [support@UpMyRank.com](mailto:support@upmyrank.com). Furthermore, all members are provided opportunities to opt-in to marketing and promotional programs provided by our advertisers through our Web site. 

**A Special Note About Children**

UpMyRank.com wants to help parents protect the privacy of children and has taken steps to obtain parental permission before children may begin the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program™ Service. UpMyRank.com does not consider our Web Site or the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program™ Service to be directed at children but some children have signed up as Members. We ask that children under 13 obtain parental permission before joining UpMyRank.com. To remove your child from UpMyRank.com membership or the UpMyRank AutoSurf Program™ Service, please contact us at [support@UpMyRank.com](mailto:support@upmyrank.com). 

**Changes to the Policy**

By registering as a member at UpMyRank.com, you agree to accept this privacy policy and are aware that our policy may change from time to time. This policy will be available on this page for members to read. Members will be notified on our home page of any change to our privacy policy. 

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact [privacy@UpMyRank.com](mailto:privacy@upmyrank.com).
